我不知道我在做什么  以前我起床
I don't know what I was doing before I got up.
我会觉得  哇  今天我要努力
I would feel like, "Wow, I'm going to work hard today!"
去把这个视频做出来  我
Go and make this video.
之前都要忙这件事情  但是
I was busy with this matter before, but when
当你同时做30个事情的时候
When you do 30 things at the same time
你会发现  我今天是要
You'll find that I'm going to...
为什么东西而努力
What are we striving for?
来着这感觉特别  特别
This feeling is especially special.
糟糕  反正这次来
Oh well, anyway, what's the purpose of this visit?
意大利我觉得挺好的一点就是
One of the good things about Italy, in my opinion, is that it's old.
老外他缺点有很多  这个我就
He has many shortcomings, that's all.
不过多赘述  但是有一点
However, I won't go into too much detail, but there is one point...
我真的觉得挺值得学的
I really think it's worth learning.
就是他们从来不为自己的
They never think of themselves
休息而有愧疚感  这个
Feeling guilty while resting
是一个我觉得很难一点  比如其实
It's something I find a bit difficult, for example...
我们比较忙特别高强度
We are quite busy and extremely stressed.
的工作环境之下
Under the influence of a high degree of working environment
经常会想  我这样会不会被
I often wonder if I'll be...
别人超过  我这样休息
Others rest like me
真的可以吗  我这样休息
Is it really okay for me to rest like this for a while?
会不会让别的同事觉得
It won't make other colleagues feel uncomfortable.
不可靠  但是我和这些
Reliable, but I and these old ones
老外聊天  他们就会说  Tim
When they chat outside, they'll say Tim
你累吗  然后我说  确实
Are you tired? Then you said yes.
有点累   他说  那  你  休息啊
He said you should rest if you're tired.
反正对他们来说  是个
Anyway, it's a...
很自然的事情  就这种
It's just a natural thing.
松弛感  我知道这和他们的生活
I know about relaxation and their lives.
环境  他们的生活状态和
Their living conditions and environment
收入什么各方面很大的
Income and other aspects are very important.
关系但是讲真的  我还是挺
But honestly, I'm still quite envious.
羡慕的  就是  你看  他们在休息
I admire them because they are resting.
他们在休息  这里的鸭子
The ducks are resting here.
也在休息  反正我希望
I'm also resting, anyway, I hope
我们大家就是该休息的时候  如果
It's time for us all to rest.
身体觉得累了  那咱就
If your body feels tired, then we'll...
歇上一些也不打紧
It's okay to take a break.